<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on COES-Publicaciones</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on COES-Publicaciones</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/linea-1/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/linea-1/publications/</guid>
      <description>Line 1 &amp;ldquo;Inequality, Conflict and Cohesion&amp;rdquo;  ISI Publications No ISI Publications Books and Chapters Interline Publications  ISI Publucations   Abufhele, A.; Torche, F. (In press)	The Normativity of Marriage and the Marriage Premium for Children&amp;rsquo;s Outcomes	American Journal of Sociology	(IF: 4.458)
  Agloni, N., Burchell, B., Piasna, A., Sehnbruch, K. (2020) Job quality in the European Employment Strategy: One step forward, two steps back?	Trasnfer: European Review of Labour and Research	(IF: 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/linea-2/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/linea-2/publications/</guid>
      <description>Line 2 &amp;ldquo;Group and Individual Interactions&amp;rdquo;  ISI Publications No ISI Publications Books and Chapters Interline Publications  ISI Publications   Angelcos, N.; Sembler, C.	(In press) Reflexividad, identidad y cambio social en la sociología crítica contemporánea	Andamios. Revista de investigación social	(IF: 0.122)
  Atria, Jorge; Castillo; Juan Carlos; Maldonado, Luis; Ramirez, Simón. (2020) Economic Elites’ Attitudes Toward Meritocracy in Chile: A Moral Economy Perspective	American Behavioral Scientist	(IF: 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/linea-3/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/linea-3/publications/</guid>
      <description>Line 3 &amp;ldquo;Politics&amp;rdquo;  ISI Publications No ISI Publications Books and Chapters Interline Publications  ISI Publications   Basaure, M., Joignant, A. y Gárate, M. (2020)	Death, Doubt, Truth and Charisma Exhumations, manipulations and enigmas surrounding the deaths of Salvador Allende and Eduardo Frei.	Memory Studies	(IF: 1.842)
  Bogliaccini, J.; Madariaga, A. (2020)	Varieties of Skills Profiles in Latin America: a reassessment of the hierarchical model of capitalism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/linea-4/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/linea-4/publications/</guid>
      <description>Line 4 &amp;ldquo;Geographies of Conflict and Cohesion&amp;rdquo;  ISI Publications No ISI Publications Books and Chapters Interline Publications  ISI Publications   Atienza, M., Fleming, D., Aroca, P. (2020)	Territorial development and mining. Insights and challenges from the Chilean case.	Resources Policy	(FI: 3.986)
  Fierro, P., Aroca, P., Navia, P. (2020)	How people access the internet and the democratic divide: Evidence from the Chilean region of Valparaiso 2017, 2018 and 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
